## Fabian Villaseñor

Modesto, CA 95354 Exionite@gmail.com (209) 896-6386

FabianVillasenor.com

linkedin.com/in/FabianVillasenor

github.com/EndingNever

#### **Technical Skills**

- Front end experience with React, Javascript, JSX, Angular, SASS, Styled Components, CSS Modules,
  React Router, React Context, Redux, TypeScript, Firebase
- Hands on backend experience with Node.js, Express, Insomnia, MySQL, jsonwebtoken, custom REST APIs, Fakestore API, OMDb API
- Experience with Github operations in a team, including team organization and communication, and managing merge conflicts

# **Projects**

# Tesla Shop Recreation <a href="https://endingnever.github.io/groupproject/">https://endingnever.github.io/groupproject/</a>

Recreation of the Tesla shop, including a small product database. Worked in a team of four, with successful github merges including resolution of conflicts

# $Mixellence \ \ \, \underline{ https://github.com/OxanaSF/mixellence}$

Website for a business which provides a bartender service. The site has a front end viewable by potential clients and an administrator dashboard only accessible with a password. The admin can change text and photos in the page without any code, through the use of Firebase.

## React Card Game https://endingnever.github.io/ReactGame/

Javascript heavy card game based on Kings Corner. A card can only be placed on another whose value is one higher. Eleven different arrays, each with their own state, are managed with the React useState hook.

# **Experience**

#### AlphaWorks, Bitwise Industries - React Apprentice

February 2022 - current

- Front End development using React, Styled Components, SASS, and custom CSS
- State, Context, custom hooks, Redux, fetch requests, React Router v5/v6
- Deployment through Github Pages, experience with Heroku,

#### E&J Gallo - Assoc. Business Systems Analyst

January 2022 - February 2022

- Business system development through ServiceNow
- Experience with Automated Test Frameworks and front-end development for service portal
- Interaction and referencing of different tables, requests, variables, and workflows

#### **Bay Valley Tech** - *Intern*

June 2021 - August 2021

- Working within a team, splitting a large project into individually manageable pieces
- Our team built a Youtube Web Player in Angular using the Youtube API
- Handling different Github branches, and merging new features when approved

#### **Bay Valley Tech** - Student

December 2020 - September 2021

- Learned the basics of coding with HTML, CSS, and Angular
- Javascript fundamentals through freecodecamp, udemy courses, practicing functions and algorithms, and building projects
- Involved Consistent coding, homework, practice, and learning

#### Doordash - Driver

April 2018 - January 2022

- Self-employed food delivery
- Responsible for all records such as car maintenance, daily miles, expenses for tax purposes
- Clean driving record

### Berkshire Hathaway- Licensed Real Estate Agent

August 2019 - November 2020

- Held open houses, following up with prospective clients
- Provide information on available homes, financing

## **Education**

#### **Modesto Junior College**

January 2022 - Current

- B.S. Computer Science for transfer
  - Includes experience with Python, C++, problem solving